How did serfdom develop in and then leave <LOC>Russia</LOC> ?
What films featured the character <PER>Popeye Doyle</PER> ?
How can I find a list of celebrities ' real names ?
What fowl grabs the spotlight after the Chinese Year of the Monkey ?
What is the full form of .com ?
What contemptible scoundrel stole the cork from my lunch ?
What team did baseball 's <ORG>St. Louis Browns</ORG> become ?
What is the oldest profession ?
What are liver enzymes ?
Name the scar-faced bounty hunter of The Old West .
When was <PER>Ozzy Osbourne</PER> born ?
Why do heavier objects travel downhill faster ?
Who was <PER>The Pride of the Yankees</PER> ?
Who killed <PER>Gandhi</PER> ?
What is considered the costliest disaster the insurance industry has ever faced ?
What sprawling <LOC>U.S.</LOC> state boasts the most airports ?
What did the only repealed amendment to the <LOC>U.S.</LOC> Constitution deal with ?
How many Jews were executed in concentration camps during WWII ?
What is `` <ORG>Nine Inch Nails</ORG> '' ?
What is an annotated bibliography ?
What is the date of Boxing Day ?
What articles of clothing are tokens in Monopoly ?
Name 11 famous martyrs .
What 's the Olympic motto ?
What is the origin of the name ` Scarlett ' ?
What 's the second-most-used vowel in English ?
Who was the inventor of silly putty ?
What is the highest waterfall in the <LOC>United States</LOC> ?
Name a golf course in <LOC>Myrtle Beach</LOC> .
Which two states enclose <LOC>Chesapeake Bay</LOC> ?
What does the abbreviation AIDS stand for ?
What does a spermologer collect ?
How many points make up a perfect fivepin bowling score ?
Which company that manufactures video-game hardware sells the `` super system '' ?
How many Community Chest cards are there in Monopoly ?
What do <ORG>Mormons</ORG> believe ?
When did the neanderthal man live ?
In what religion was <PER>Isis</PER> the nature goddess ?
Where do the adventures of `` <PER>The Swiss Family Robinson</PER> '' take place ?
What relative of the racoon is sometimes known as the cat-bear ?
How can I register my website in <ORG>Yahoo</ORG> for free ?
What was cash-conscious Colonel <PER>Edwin L. Drake</PER> the first to drill ?
How many people in the world speak French ?
How many inches over six feet is the Venus de Milo ?
How do they find or choose witnesses to an execution ?
What 1920s cowboy star rode <PER>Tony the Wonder Horse</PER> ?
What cocktail inspired <PER>John Doxat</PER> to write the book Stirred-Not Shaken ?
What ISPs exist in the <LOC>Caribbean</LOC> ?
How do you ask a total stranger out on a date ?
What weapon is the mythological character <PER>Apollo</PER> most proficient with ?
What country do the <LOC>Galapagos Islands</LOC> belong to ?
What is ethology ?
Who was the prophet of the <ORG>Muslim people</ORG> ?
Where did the term `` 86ed '' come from ?
Who is <PER>Snoopy</PER> 's arch-enemy ?
What is the nature of learning ?
What 's the only color <PER>Johnny Cash</PER> wears on stage ?
What 's the term for a young fox ?
What <LOC>U.S.</LOC> state lived under six flags ?
What is the <LOC>Kashmir</LOC> issue ?
Where is the <LOC>Loop</LOC> ?
What does `` extended definition '' mean and how would one write a paper on it ?
What country 's capital is <LOC>Tirana</LOC> ?
What is titanium ?
Who do <PER>Herb</PER> and <PER>Tootsie</PER> live next door to ?
Which city has the oldest relationship as a sisterðcity with <LOC>Los Angeles</LOC> ?
What is a caldera ?
Why do people get calluses ?
What are the names of the tourist attractions in <LOC>Reims</LOC> ?
What are <PER>Cushman</PER> and <PER>Wakefield</PER> known for ?
What body of water does the <LOC>Danube River</LOC> flow into ?
Who is the founder of <ORG>Scientology</ORG> ?
What does the six-footed Musca domestica become when it enters a house ?
What is the history of skateboarding ?
Who starred in Singing in the Rain and The Singing Nun ?
How do I make fuel bricks from recycled newspaper ?
What 19th-century painter died in the <LOC>Marquesas Islands</LOC> ?
The corpus callosum is in what part of the body ?
How do I log on to home page at Headquarters <ORG>U.S. European Command</ORG> ?
What country did the <ORG>Nazis</ORG> occupy for 1 , CD NNS IN NNP NNP NNP .
What is <LOC>Nebraska</LOC> 's most valuable resource ?
How many species of the Great White shark are there ?
What is the origin of head lice ?
What is the nickname for the <LOC>state of Mississippi</LOC> ?
What was the first domesticated bird ?
How many villi are found in the small intestine ?
What country did King <PER>Wenceslas</PER> rule ?
What is a fear of shadows ?
Who were the five <PER>Marx</PER> brothers ?
In which year was <LOC>New Zealand</LOC> excluded from the <ORG>ANZUS alliance</ORG> ?
When did <ORG>CNN</ORG> begin broadcasting ?
What causes the body to shiver in cold temperatures ?
What are bear and bull markets ?
What <PER>J.R.R. Tolkien</PER> book features <PER>Bilbo Baggins</PER> as the central character ?
What is `` dew point '' ?
What is the meaning of <PER>Jesus</PER> ?
What company 's logo is a `` W '' in a circle ?
What is the definition of a cascade ?
When did Rococo painting and architecture flourish ?
What country 's national passenger rail system is called Via ?
Who invented Make-up ?
What is the origin of the word `` attic '' ?
What did <PER>Delilah</PER> do to <PER>Samson</PER> 's hair ?
What kind of animals were in the Paleozoic era ?
Which of the following was Rhodes Scholar ?
Who comprised the now-defunct comic book team known as <PER>the Champions</PER> ?
How do you make a paintball ?
What <LOC>U.S.</LOC> state is <LOC>Fort Knox</LOC> in ?
What is a female rabbit called ?
Where is the highest point in <LOC>Japan</LOC> ?
Where do chihuahuas come from ?
Where does <PER>Barney Rubble</PER> go to work after he drops <PER>Fred</PER> off in the `` Flintstones '' cartoon series ?
What are the world 's four oceans ?
What 's the only work by <PER>Michelangelo</PER> that bears his signature ?
What is the largest snake in the world ?
In what medium is <PER>Stuart Hamblen</PER> considered to be the first singing cowboy ?
Where on the Internet can I find a song lyrics database similar to the International Lyrics Server ?
How much money does a back injury lawsuit get ?
What 's the common name for acetylsalicylic acid ?
What does the <LOC>Georgetown</LOC> `` Hoya '' mean ?
Where can I find a list of `` classic '' books 5th and 6th graders should read ?
Which two products use a tiger as their symbol ?
How is the election of a new Pope announced to the world ?
How long does it take for your blood to make one complete trip through the body ?
How do chickens have baby chicks ?
What is the historical relationship of <ORG>Catholic Church</ORG> and bingo ?
How was the element calcium named ?
What crooner joined <ORG>The Andrews Sisters</ORG> for Pistol Packin Mama ?
What piano company claims its product is the `` Instrument of the immortals '' ?
When did the Bounty mutiny take place ?
What novel inspired the movie BladeRunner ?
What is a transistor ?
What is a film starring <PER>Jude Law</PER> ?
What Hollywood dog died in the arms of <PER>Jean Harlow</PER> in 1932 ?
What are the most common elements in the <LOC>Earth</LOC> 's crust ?
How much would it cost to purchase a 2-foot-square party tent , with sides , ?
What actress has received the most Oscar nominations ?
What are equity securities ?
What is gymnophobia ?
How many years do fossils take to form ?
Where is the <LOC>Orinoco</LOC> ?
What was the name of the `` Little Rascals '' dog ?
What city boasts <LOC>Penn 's Landing</LOC> , on the banks of the <LOC>Delaware river</LOC> ?
What Broadway musical was inspired by <PER>Cervantes</PER> 's <PER>Don Quixote</PER> ?
What is the origin of the word , JJ .
How many hostages were killed in the Entebbe raid ?
How you can raise your IQ ?
What does INRI stand for when used on <PER>Jesus</PER> ' cross ?
Who produces Spumante ?
Who earns their money the hard way ?
Who founded the <ORG>People 's Temple Commune</ORG> ?
What athlete makes the most money from sports merchandise sales ?
How many bends are there in a standard paper clip ?
Who discovered electricity ?
What part of your body contains the corpus callosum ?
Who was the first American in space ?
What two South American countries do n't border <LOC>Brazil</LOC> ?
What album put <ORG>The Beatles</ORG> on the cover of <ORG>Time</ORG> in 1967 ?
What poem contains the line , `` grow old with me the best is yet to be '' .
What is a dental root canal ?
What war did the Wanna-Go-Home Riots occur after ?
What is the busiest air travel season ?
What 's the colored part of the eye called ?
What are hook worms ?
Where is the Rose Bowl played ?
Which Japanese car maker had its biggest percentage of sale in the domestic market ?
Who is the mayor of <LOC>Marbella</LOC> ?
What sun-blasted , 14-mile wide valley is just north of the <LOC>Mojave desert</LOC> ?
In what year did <PER>Thatcher</PER> become prime minister ?
How many months does it take the <LOC>moon</LOC> to revolve around the <LOC>Earth</LOC> ?
Where are the 49 steps ?
In what year was <PER>De Gaulle</PER> elected president of <LOC>France</LOC> ?
Who sings the themes for `` Dawson 's Creek '' and `` Felicity '' ?
Who directed `` Jaws '' ?
On what T.V. show could <PER>Tom Terrific</PER> be found ?
What Indian tribe is <ORG>F Troop</ORG> perpetually doing battle with ?
Where did Indian Pudding come from ?
Why do some clothing labels say `` Use a nonchlorine bleach '' ?
How many colonies were involved in the American Revolution ?
What is the name of the city that <PER>Maurizio Pellegrin</PER> lives in ?
Where can I find pictorial directions on how to build a very simple treehouse ?
What game 's board shows the territories of <LOC>Irkutsk</LOC> , <LOC>Yakutsk</LOC> and <LOC>Kamchatka</LOC> ?
What is the name of the managing director of <ORG>Apricot Computer</ORG> ?
What is the occupation of <PER>Nicholas Cage</PER> ?
Why do horseshoes bring luck ?
What is the 401 , K , plan ?
What causes pneumonia ?
What are the three winter months in the <LOC>southern hemisphere</LOC> ?
What does gringo mean ?
What country contains <LOC>Africa</LOC> 's northernmost point ?
What therapy attempts to elicit the `` primal scream '' ?
Where is the <LOC>Kalahari desert</LOC> ?
Which <LOC>Ventura County</LOC> police department seized the largest cocaine shipment in it 's history ?
What city is sometimes called <LOC>Gotham</LOC> ?
What dangles over the tongue from the palate ?
Who created <PER>Dennis the Menace</PER> ?
What dummy received an honorary degree from <ORG>Northwestern University</ORG> ?
When was the first <ORG>Wall Street Journal</ORG> published ?
What countries have the largest areas of forest ?
How do I start a web based business ?
Name <PER>Alvin</PER> 's brothers
What is Eagle 's syndrome styloid process ?
How did <PER>Jayne Mansfield</PER> die ?
When did the royal wedding of Prince <PER>Andrew</PER> and <PER>Fergie</PER> take place ?
What actor said in A Day at the Races : `` Either he 's dead or my watch has stopped '' ?
What explorer was nicknamed <PER>Iberia 's Pilot</PER> ?
<ORG>CNN</ORG> began broadcasting in what year ?
What is a ball that hits the foul pole called ?
What makes hamburgers taste like steakburgers ?
Which company created the Internet browser Mosaic ?
What are the rites accompanying the circumcision of a newly born-child in <ORG>Judaism</ORG> called ?
What was the education system in the 1960 's ?
What South American city has the world 's highest commercial landing field ?
How can I find out which cities have cable-modem access ?
What is <PER>Betsy Ross</PER> famous for ?
How many species of sharks are there ?
What is `` snoogans '' ?
How many people are there in the world ?
What shrubs can be planted that will be safe from deer ?
What organization 's offices were broken into at <LOC>Watergate</LOC> in 1972 ?
What is the design of the ship Titanic ?
What does S.O.S. stand for ?
Name a technique widely used to detect birth defects ?
What is the daily requirement of folic acid for an expectant mother ?
What is the `` 7-minute cigarette '' ?
What four forms does gold occur in ?
What is the acreage of the <LOC>Chappellet vineyard</LOC> ?
How do you correctly say the word ` qigong ' ?
When did <PER>beethoven</PER> die ?
How much does a new railroad coal car cost ?
What two European countries entered the War of American Independence against the British ?
What is the filmmakers collabrative ?
What Russian composer 's Prelude in C Sharp Minor brought him fame and fortune ?
What caused <PER>Harry Houdini</PER> 's death ?
Who was the mother of the man who would not be king , the duke of <LOC>Windsor</LOC> ?
How many revolutions does a standard LP make in three minutes ?
What is the name of the tallest mountain in the world ?
Where can I find a review of Nightmare on Elm Street in a film journal ?
What 's the slowest Olympic swimming stroke ?
What was the name of the first Russian astronaut to do a spacewalk ?
What disease is transmitted by the Anopheles mosquito ?
What rum is so `` mixable '' it is a one-brand bar ?
How many South American countries have the letter Z in their names ?
What is the contents of proposition 98 ?
Where was <PER>George Washington</PER> born ?
Who wrote NN DT NNP NNP '' ?
What is paracetamol ?
What are the powers and weaknesses of <PER>Green Lantern</PER> 's ring ?
Which mosquito 's bite draws blood , DT NN CC DT NN .
When was the first steel mill in the <LOC>United States</LOC> built ?
What diminutive American female gymnast stole the show at the 1984 Olympics ?
What is the origin of the name Katie ?
What schools in the <LOC>Washington , DC</LOC> NN NN VBP NN NN NN NN .
When did the <LOC>Berlin Wall</LOC> go up ?
Who is <PER>Terrence Malick</PER> ?
What instrument is <PER>Ray Charles</PER> best known for playing ?
What 's the meaning of the Latin battle cry : Ad arma , ad arma .
What <LOC>Las Vegas</LOC> hotel burned in November , 1980 , with the loss of 84 lives ?
When did <LOC>Mount St. Helen</LOC> last have a significant eruption ?
CNN is the abbreviation for what ?
When did World War I start ?
How many feet are there in a fathom ?
What is a <LOC>Canada</LOC> two-penny black ?
What European city do <PER>Nicois</PER> live in ?
How can I find out what year a Beanie Baby was introduced ?
What is the classic definition of tragic hero ?
To what does <ORG>Microsoft</ORG> 's Windows 3 owe its success ?
Who was President of <LOC>Afghanistan</LOC> in 1994 ?
What are other ways of getting stretch marks besides pregnancy , weight loss , and weight lifting ?
What did brontosauruses eat ?
What color bottles do good <LOC>Rhine</LOC> wines come in ?
Who was the lead actress in the movie ` Sleepless in Seattle ' ?
Who are the two sons of <PER>Ozzie</PER> and <PER>Harriet Nelson</PER> ?
What is molybdenum ?
When is Boxing Day ?
What is the lowest level of the American judiciary ?
When was the battle of the Somme fought ?
How many people did <PER>Randy Craft</PER> kill ?
What 's the official animal of <LOC>Canada</LOC> ?
When did <PER>Spielberg</PER> direct `` Jaws '' ?
What is the size of the largest akita ?
What animal has the biggest eyes ?
What is <LOC>California</LOC> 's capital ?
Who was the author of the book about computer hackers called `` The Cuckoo 's Egg : Tracking a Spy Through the Maze of Computer Espionage '' ?
Who was the founding member of the <ORG>Pink Floyd</ORG> band ?
What European country is home to the beer-producing city of <LOC>Budweis</LOC> ?
How do I find the balance of my social security account ?
What is the history of Valentine 's Day cards ?
Where was <PER>Christopher Columbus</PER> born ?
What do Italians call <LOC>Florence</LOC> ?
How do you get to the top of the <LOC>Eiffel Tower</LOC> ?
What does ` PSI ' stand for ?
What sea did the Romans call <LOC>mare nostrum</LOC> ?
What 's the term for a bet before cards are dealt ?
Which came first , according to Genesis 1 : 2 : 22 - the chicken or the egg ?
What city did the <PER>Flintstones</PER> live in ?
What is Latin for incompetent ?
What chemicals are used in lethal injection ?
What toy company is the world 's No.1 maker of female apparel ?
What board game does a `` wood-pusher '' play poorly ?
Which Doonesbury character was likely to turn into a werewolf ?
What is the abbreviation for micro ?
What are the 7 articles of the constitution ?
Who has won the most Super Bowls ?
What does NASDAQ stand for ?
What is BPH ?
What is the fastest commercial automobile that can be bought in the <LOC>US</LOC> ?
What stadium do the <ORG>Miami Dolphins</ORG> play their home games in ?
Who has the only speaking role in `` Silent Movie '' ?
Why is poop sometimes different colors ?
What was <PER>Einstein</PER> 's IQ ?
What day was <LOC>Pearl Harbor</LOC> attacked in 1942 ?
What girl 's name is `` Teddy '' an affectionate form of ?
What state is <PER>John F. Kennedy</PER> buried in ?
What is the best way to remove wallpaper ?
What <LOC>U.S.</LOC> state has an element named for it ?
What company tabulates the ballots in voting for the Academy Awards ?
How did the tradition of best man start ?
How many years ago did the ship Titanic sink ?
What is the deepest area of the <LOC>Arctic Ocean</LOC> ?
What are Halloween 's colors ?
How is silk screening done ?
What is the latitude and longitude of <LOC>El Paso</LOC> , <LOC>Texas</LOC> ?
Who made a boat out of gopher wood ?
Where can I find a `` Fifth Element '' screensaver ?
Which <LOC>Bloom County</LOC> resident wreaks havoc with a computer ?
How do you match a name to a social security number ?
How does a rainbow form ?
What is the normal resting heart rate of a healthy adult ?
What is the population of <LOC>Ohio</LOC> ?
How many calories are there in a Big Mac ?
Hazmat stands for what ?
What creature scares people in the film `` Jaws '' ?
What part did <PER>John Peter Zenger</PER> play in the deveopment of the newspaper in <LOC>America</LOC> ?
Who followed <PER>Caesar</PER> ?
What are the four elements ?
Who was the first woman golfer to earn a million ?
What 's the tallest piece on a chessboard ?
What is Answers.com 's address ?
Where can I buy movies on videotape online ?
Who does the advertizing for <ORG>Frito-Lay</ORG> ?
Who is the leading competitor of <ORG>Trans Union</ORG> Company ?
What product did <PER>Robert Conrad</PER> dare people to knock off his shoulder ?
Who invented the radio ?
What 's the American dollar equivalent for 8 pounds in the <LOC>U.K.</LOC> ?
What are the different approaches of systems analysis ?
How do doctors diagnose bone cancer ?
Who is the man behind the pig-the man who pulls the strings and speaks for Miss <PER>Piggy</PER> ?
What is the speed of the <LOC>Mississippi River</LOC> ?
What are the developmental stages of a swimmer ?
What actor first portrayed <PER>James Bond</PER> ?
What ocean is the largest in the world ?
Who was the first American poet to win the Nobel Prize for literature , in 1948 ?
What year did <PER>Jack Nicklaus</PER> join the <ORG>Professional Golfers Association</ORG> tour ?
How many sonnets did <PER>Shakespeare</PER> write ?
What causes the redness in your cheeks when you blush ?
Who won the Nobel Peace Prize in 1991 ?
Who are the <ORG>Challengers of the Unknown</ORG> ?
Define the <ORG>Pheonix Club</ORG> ?
Which city did Christian Crusaders fight to recapture from the <ORG>Muslims</ORG> ?
What does it mean `` Rupee Depreciates '' ?
What gaming devices were dubbed `` Mississippi marbles '' and `` Memphis dominoes '' ?
Who was the first coach of the <ORG>Cleveland Browns</ORG> ?
How successful is arometherapy ?
What Jewish holiday saw the start of the 1973 Mideast War ?
How does a copier work ?
What is the speed of the <LOC>Mississippi River</LOC> ?
Who said of Super Bowl III in 1969 : `` We 'll win- I guarantee it '' ?
What is <PER>Dudley Do-Right</PER> 's horse 's name ?
Who declared : `` I am down on whores and I shan 't stop ripping them '' ?
Where does chocolate come from ?
What TV game show once saw a contestant admit to picking his toes in the shower ?
What Soviet leader owned a Rolls-Royce ?
Where can I find a case on Individuals with Disabilities Education Act of 1991 ?
What war did <PER>Florence Nightingale</PER> tend the troops in ?
Who wrote the song , `` Stardust '' ?
How many <ORG>Beatles</ORG> ' records went #1 ?
Who is the only prime minister of <LOC>Canada</LOC> to serve 22 years but not necessarily consecutively ?
What is the abbreviation of the company name ` <ORG>General Motors</ORG> ' ?
What mountains lie between the <LOC>Arkansas</LOC> and <LOC>Missouri rivers</LOC> ?
Who received the Will Rogers Award in 1989 ?
What is the function of RAM ?
What 's the closest G2 Spectrum Yellow Dwarf to <LOC>Earth</LOC> ?
How many equal angles are there in an isosceles triangle ?
What is the fear of cockroaches called ?
What <ORG>CBS</ORG> soap opera was interrupted by the bulletin of <PER>John F. Kennedy</PER> 's assassination ?
What is the use of a 24-hour clock instead of a 12-hour clock ?
What was the name of the lawyer who represented <PER>Randy Craft</PER> ?
What <LOC>United States</LOC> President had dreamed that he was assassinated ?
What film did <PER>Lee Marvin</PER> win the 1965 best actor Oscar for ?
Where is <LOC>Basque country</LOC> located ?
What product does `` Mrs. <PER>Olsen</PER> '' promote ?
What time of day did Emperor <PER>Hirohito</PER> die ?
What is dry ice ?
What 's the most powerful card in Euchre ?
What does `` intractable plantar keratoma '' mean ?
How many years did it take <PER>James Joyce</PER> to write Ulysses ?
What crop failure caused the Irish Famine ?
What South Korean city is served by <LOC>Kimpo International Airport</LOC> ?
How many types of dogs ' tails are there - three
What is the longest-running television series ?
What predators exist on <LOC>Antarctica</LOC> ?
What is the difference between a generator and an alternator ?
How is energy created ?
What beer advertised that it had `` three rings '' ?
What is the quantity of American soldiers still unaccounted for from the Vietnam war ?
What golfing accessory was patented by <PER>George Grant</PER> on December 12
What are the different types of plastic ?
How is it correct to say ` qigong ' ?
What was the highest mountain on <LOC>earth</LOC> before <LOC>Mount Everest</LOC> was discovered ?
Where was the <LOC>Ligurian Republic</LOC> , 1797-185 , ?
What country 's people are the top television watchers ?
When was the women 's suffrage amendment ratified ?
What Polynesian people inhabit <LOC>New Zealand</LOC> ?
What movie tour of the Roman empire features the admonition : `` Row well and live '' ?
What <LOC>Nevada</LOC> center has been dubbed <LOC>The Biggest Little City in the World</LOC> ?
What President lived at <LOC>219 North Delaware Street</LOC> , <LOC>Independence</LOC> , <LOC>Missouri</LOC> ?
Give a reason for American Indians oftentimes dropping out of school .
Where must a soccer goalie stand to be permitted to handle the ball ?
What is the difference between classical conditioning and operant conditioning ?
In what <LOC>U.S.</LOC> state was the first woman governor elected ?
What are some interesting facts and information about dogsledding ?
What year did <PER>Hitler</PER> die ?
What famous model was married to <PER>Billy Joel</PER> ?
What kind of animal is <PER>Babar</PER> ?
What is <PER>Jane Goodall</PER> known for ?
What killed <PER>Bob Marley</PER> ?
How much money are <PER>Dumbo</PER> 's ears insured for ?
Who danced into stardom with <PER>Fred Astaire</PER> in 1941 's You 'll Never Get Rich ?
Who is <PER>Stein Eriksen</PER> ?
What does the name Billie mean ?
Who is the fastest swimmer in the world ?
What is the highest peak in <LOC>Africa</LOC> ?
Where is <ORG>Procter & Gamble</ORG> headquartered in the <LOC>U.S.</LOC> ?
What desert has been called <LOC>The Garden of Allah</LOC> ?
What do bicornate animals have two of ?
What function does a community 's water tower serve ?
What is a fear of weakness ?
How many miles is it to <LOC>Ohio</LOC> from <LOC>North Carolina</LOC> ?
How much snow equals an inch of rain ?
What does G.M.T. stand for ?
What does Inuit and Eskimo mean ?
What song served as the closing theme of The Johnny Cash Show ?
What field sport did dentist <PER>William Beers</PER> promote and write a standard book of rules for ?
How do I tie dye clothes ?
When does the average teenager first have intercourse ?
Why doesn 't www.answers.com have any answers to my questions ?
What actor 's autobiography is titled All My Yesterdays ?
What Russian master spy lived in the <LOC>U.S.</LOC> under the name <PER>Emil Goldfus</PER> ?
Where 's the 19th hole on a golf course ?
What 's nature 's purpose for tornadoes ?
Who played the original Charlie 's Angels ?
Where can I find a person 's address from a telephone number ?
What English word comes from the Old French covrefeu , meaning cover fire ?
What musical instrument did <PER>Prewitt</PER> play in <PER>James Jones</PER> 's From Here to Eternity ?
Where did <PER>Sarge Steel</PER> get his metal hand ?
What makes popcorn pop ?
Who wrote The Night of the Iguana ?
Where does your hair grow the fastest ?
What country did King <PER>Gustav V</PER> reign over from 197 to 195 ?
Who painted Mother and Child ?
What is the speed of the <LOC>Mississippi River</LOC> ?
In what area of the world was the Six Day War fought ?
What is the brightest star visible from <LOC>Earth</LOC> ?
What film marked <PER>Robert Redford</PER> 's directorial debut ?
What was <PER>Mao</PER> 's second name ?
What film or films has <PER>Jude Law</PER> appeared in ?
Where do hyenas live ?
Who is the `` <PER>Queen Mother</PER> '' ?
What 's the most commonly-spoken language in <LOC>Belgium</LOC> ?
Who has more DNA - a man or a woman ?
What are Maid-Rites ?
What children 's tale contains the line : `` Come , Cinderslut , and hold this skein of wool for me '' ?
What level of government or governmental agency is responsible for dealing with racism ?
How many referees work a soccer game ?
What cocktail do you concoct with whisky and sweet vermouth ?
How do you say `` fresh '' in Spanish ?
What do bee hives do in cranberry bogs ?
What caused the <ORG>Lynmouth</ORG> floods ?
When is the Tulip Festival in <LOC>Michigan</LOC> ?
Who came up with the name , El Nino ?
What movie did <PER>Madilyn Kahn</PER> star in with <PER>Gene Wilder</PER> ?
What type of bridge is the <LOC>Golden Gate Bridge</LOC> ?
What dictator has the nickname `` <PER>El Maximo</PER> '' ?
What stereo manufacturer is `` Slightly ahead of its time '' ?
What <LOC>U.S.</LOC> city is <LOC>The Queen of the Pacific</LOC> ?
What TV sitcom character had the maiden name <PER>Ethel Potter</PER> ?
What was the first Lifesaver flavor ?
Who kept the most famous diary in the English language ?
Where can I find out the top 1 singles ?
How many degrees cooler is the inside of a cucumber than the air outside ?
What Spanish artist painted Crucifixion ?
What is the Jewish bible called ?
Why is the grass green ?
What is a firewall ?
What spy novelist served as <LOC>Moscow</LOC> correspondent for <ORG>Reuter</ORG> and <ORG>The Times of London</ORG> ?
Which oil company almost picked a word that meant `` stalled car '' in Japanese as its new international name ?
How long does it take for <PER>Spider-Man</PER> 's web to evaporate ?
Who was <PER>Randy Steven Craft</PER> 's lawyer ?
What was known as the Spice Island ?
Who was the first host of Person to Person ?
Name the Ranger who was always after <PER>Yogi Bear</PER> .
What deck of cards includes the Wheel of Fortune , the Lovers , and Death ?
What does the <PER>Statue of Liberty</PER> wear on her feet ?
Who is the superstar in rent-a-cars ?
<LOC>McCarren Airport</LOC> is located in what city ?
What household facility contains a float ball , ballcock , and overflow tube ?
What was the name of <PER>Betty Boop</PER> 's dog ?
What fraction of a beaver 's life is spent swimming ?
What was the <LOC>Bridge of San Luis Rey</LOC> made of ?
What do economists do ?
What country has the largest sheep population ?
What do I need to do to take my dog with me to live in <LOC>Dominica</LOC> , <LOC>West Indies</LOC> for a year ?
What country is the world 's largest importer of cognac ?
How many years is Johnnie Walker Black Label aged ?
What does SIDS stand for ?
What is <LOC>Grenada</LOC> 's main commodity export ?
How much would a black-and-white 1-cent stamp be worth , <PER>Thomas Jefferson</PER> on it , ?
What makes a clitoris sensitive ?
What country has the most time zones , with 11 ?
What `` magic '' does <PER>Mandrake</PER> employ ?
Who is the president of <ORG>Stanford University</ORG> ?
Whose first presidential order was : `` Let 's get this goddamn thing airborne '' ?
What was introduced commercially by <ORG>Bayer A.G.</ORG> of <LOC>Leverkusen</LOC> , in 1899 ?
What city is <LOC>Logan Airport</LOC> in ?
What is a nanometer ?
How many innings are there in a regulation softball game ?
When did <ORG>CNN</ORG> go on the air ?
What is the largest city on the <LOC>Great Lakes</LOC> ?
What is the telephone number for the <ORG>University of Kentucky</ORG> ?
Who invented baseball ?
How many wives did <PER>Brigham Young</PER> have ?
What product on the market is good for hiding facial scars ?
How long is the <LOC>Coney Island</LOC> boardwalk ?
What city gained renown for its pea-soup fogs ?
What does `` Janelle '' mean ?
How do I get another city 's newspaper ?
Name a movie about the Sioux Indians starring <PER>Kevin Costner</PER> .
Who was shot in the back during a Poker game in <LOC>Deadwood</LOC> , the <LOC>Dakota</LOC> territory ?
What are the distinct physical characterstics of the Arabian horse ?
What is a fear of thunder ?
What animal has killed the most people ?
How many colleges are in <LOC>Wyoming</LOC> ?
What Russian seaport has a name meaning `` <LOC>Lord of the East</LOC> '' ?
Where can stocks be traded on-line ?
When was the Battle of Hastings ?
What kind of file has the extension .dbf ?
When did <PER>Muhammad</PER> live ?
What then-derogatory term was applied to the painters <PER>Monet</PER> , <PER>Sisley</PER> , <PER>Pissarro</PER> , <PER>Renoir</PER> and <PER>Degas</PER> ?
What is a wop ?
Where do rocks come from ?
How do I stop background noise in a car stereo ?
Where do people mountain climb in <LOC>Nepal</LOC> ?
What is the best college in the country ?
What is viscosity ?
What was the name of the sitcom that <PER>Alyssa Milano</PER> starred in with <PER>Tony Danza</PER> ?
What are the Nordic nations ?
Where on the Internet can I get information about the Fifth Amendment on the American Bill of Rights ?
What <LOC>U.S.</LOC> state borders <LOC>Illinois</LOC> to the north ?
Name a film in which <PER>Jude Law</PER> acted .
What is the temperature for baking Peachy Oat Muffins ?
What is a fear of bees ?
What <PER>Vladimir Nabokov</PER> novel features Professor <PER>Humbert</PER> in love with a 12-year-old girl ?
What is a green bog ?
Where did the myth of <PER>Santa Claus</PER> originate ?
What does a chairbound basophobic fear ?
What city is served by <LOC>Logan International Airport</LOC> ?
What wrestling star became `` <PER>The Incredible Hulk</PER> '' ?
What attracts tourists to <LOC>Reims</LOC> ?
What game do <PER>Steve McQueen</PER> and <PER>Edward G. Robinson</PER> play in The Cincinnati Kid ?
What fastener did <PER>Whitcomb Judson</PER> patent in 1893 ?
What 's an auberge in <LOC>France</LOC> ?
Who was the star of the 1965 Broadway hit Golden Boy ?
Where is <ORG>Procter & Gamble</ORG> based in the <LOC>U.S.</LOC> ?
What army was founded by <PER>William Booth</PER> and his wife <PER>Catherine</PER> ?
What does ribavirin consist of ?
Name the soft drink that is `` number one in the sun . ''
What is the web address of the list of e-mail addresses of members of the <ORG>House of Representatives</ORG> ?
What was her real name ?
Why are the ears your center of balance ?
Who invented the toothbrush ?
What was the name of that popular song the <ORG>Creeps</ORG> sang ?
Where is the <PER>Abominable Snowman</PER> said to wander ?
What is a fear of being alone ?
How many dots make up the symbol for `` because '' ?
What do you get by adding Lactobacillus bulgaricus to milk ?
When reading classified ads , what does EENTY : other stand for ?
How many hearts does an octopus have ?
What plant has the largest seed ?
What was the only country you were allowed to drive into <LOC>Israel</LOC> from in 1979 ?
What 's approaching when a cyclist shouts : `` Oil '' ?
What baseball star turned down a $1 , 000-a-year contract because he felt he had n't earned it ?
What kind of sport is often associated with <ORG>hooligans</ORG> ?
What video game hero do some of his fans call <PER>Chomper</PER> ?
How many holes are there in a tenpin bowling ball ?
In What city or state do the most gay men live in ?
What TV comediennes 's characters include former movie star <PER>Nora Desmond</PER> , secretary Mrs. <PER>Wiggins</PER> and a housewife named <PER>Eunice</PER> ?
What is `` the bear of beers '' ?
Name the operating system that runs on IBM-compatible machines .
What does the name `` Justin '' mean ?
What percentage of the body is muscle ?
What color of dry wine should be served with veal roasts and chops ?
What is a golf ball made of ?
What is the <ORG>Amish</ORG> religion ?
What does an average daycare provider get paid in <LOC>New England</LOC> ?
What was the name of the 187s Irish terrorist group in <LOC>Pennsylvania</LOC> mining areas ?
Who played the <PER>Ringo Kid</PER> in the 1939 film Stagecoach ?
Who died 1 feet from where <PER>John F. Kennedy</PER> did ?
What is the `` coppertop '' battery ?
What sign is The Water Carrier the zodiacal symbol for ?
What animals do you find in the stock market ?
What is color ?
When is the site www.questions.com going to open ?
What did <PER>Shostakovich</PER> write for <PER>Rostropovich</PER> ?
What first name was <PER>Nipsy Russell</PER> given at birth ?
How can I get some free technical information on Electric Vehicle ?
Who is the youngest of the <ORG>Beatles</ORG> ?
How did shipyard inspector <PER>James J. Kilroy</PER> designate equipment as being satisfactory ?
What is a Jellicle Cat ?
Where can I find the best free evidence for debate about <LOC>Russia</LOC> ?
What is <PER>Bill Gates</PER> of <ORG>Microsoft</ORG> E-mail address ?
What is the second hardest substance ?
Why did several <LOC>San Diego</LOC> schools stop serving apples to students ?
What Russian city boasts the <LOC>Hermitage Museum</LOC> ?
When is Bastille Day ?
What makes a tornado turn ?
How many shots can a stock M16 hold ?
What two colors are you blind to if you suffer from protanopia ?
Why do n't you guys have some sort of contest where you ask a question and whoever finds the answers wins a prize ?
Who is <PER>Coronado</PER> ?
What was the name of the movie that starred <PER>Sharon Stone</PER> and <PER>Arnold Schwarzenegger</PER> ?
What is artificial intelligence ?
What do flatfish eat ?
Who was the first Holy Roman Emperor ?
What can I use to remove the stubborn gummed labels from some diskettes ?
What day of the week sees the most fatal car accidents ?
What is the origin of the word , magic ?
What sport do you shag flies in ?
What is white chocolate ?
Where is <LOC>Trinidad</LOC> ?
Name the organization that is presided by a Security Council .
Who graced the airwaves with such pearls as `` Do ya lo-o-ove me ? Get naked , baby ! '' ?
What kind of wine is Spumante ?
Who portrayed portly criminologist <PER>Carl Hyatt</PER> on Checkmate ?
How do you say I love you in Spanish ?
What does the name Gina mean ?
What is the most advanced handheld calculator in the world ?
How fast is light ?
What is the belt of low pressure around the <LOC>equator</LOC> called ?
What are shooting stars ?
Whom did the <ORG>Chicago Bulls</ORG> beat in the 1993 championship ?
When was the first American encyclopedia published ?
What 's the tallest building in <LOC>New York City</LOC> ?
How is Easter Sunday 's date determined ?
What is the Motto for the <LOC>State of Maryland</LOC> ?
Who is <PER>Desmond Tutu</PER> ?
Where can I find information on the Narragansett Indians and other tribes in <LOC>Rhode Island</LOC> ?
Name a tiger that is extinct .
How many quarters equal a pound ?
What kind of books does <ORG>Fodor</ORG> 's publish ?
What are the first names of <PER>Rowan</PER> and <PER>Martin</PER> , the stars of TV 's Laugh-In ?
What chapter of the Bible has the most verses ?
Who is the worst <LOC>US</LOC> President ever ?
What Asian leader was known as <PER>The Little Brown Saint</PER> ?
What is the abbreviated expression for the <ORG>National Bureau of Investigation</ORG> ?
How fast does the fastest car go ?
What is the highest mountain in the world ?
What arch can you see from the <LOC>Place de la Concorde</LOC> ?
Who sings the song `` Drink to me with thine eyes '' by <PER>Ben Johnson</PER> ?
How long should a person wash their hands before they are clean ?
Which way do you turn your Bic to increase the flame - clockwise or counterclockwise ?
Which is the wealthiest country in the world ?
How can I find a phone number of someone if I only know their email address ?
How can you contact play producers and promoters on-line ?
Who is the monarch of the <LOC>United Kingdom</LOC> ?
What is a fear of passing high objects ?
What do players try to do when the music stops in a game of musical chairs ?
What are the top ten most common girl names in the <LOC>US</LOC> ?
Why is black the color of mourning in the West ?
What is the rarest coin ?
What <PER>Judith Rossner</PER> novel was made into a film starring <PER>Diane Keaton</PER> ?
Which country is <LOC>Australia</LOC> 's largest export market ?
Where is the <LOC>Kentucky Horse Park</LOC> located ?
What is a fear of parasites ?
In what Olympic Games did <PER>Nadia Comaneci</PER> become popular ?
Who does data collection in tourism ?
What was the name of the daughter of the <LOC>Virginia</LOC> chief Powhatan that married <PER>John Rolfe</PER> ?
What is the leading pecan and peanut growing state ?
What does a nihilist believe in ?
What did <PER>Richard Feynman</PER> say upon hearing he would receive the Nobel Prize in Physics ?
In what sport are these following numbers relevant : 118 , 126 , 134 , 142 , 15 , 158 , 167 , 177 , and 19 ?
Who were the four famous founders of <ORG>United Artists</ORG> ?
What 2 statues did <LOC>France</LOC> give to other countries ?
What are amphibians ?
How many sperm cells are in an average ejaculation ?
Name the disposable razor that `` costs about 19 cents . ''
How far do you have to run if you hit a home run ?
Who was the only <LOC>U.S.</LOC> President to wear a Nazi uniform ?
<PER>Woodrow Wilson</PER> served as president of what university ?
Where are the tropical rain forest distributions ?
What 's the nickname of oddsmaker <PER>Jimmy Snyder</PER> ?
What is the fear of being loved ?
What was the number of people that <PER>Randy Steven Craft</PER> was convicted of killing ?
What was Queen <PER>Victoria</PER> 's title regarding <LOC>India</LOC> ?
How is a hydrogen bomb different from a nuclear bomb ?
How far can a man travel in outer space ?
Where was <PER>Lincoln</PER> assassinated ?
What type of food makes you fat ?
What is the name of the chronic neurological autoimmune disease which attacks the protein sheath that surrounds nerve cells causing a gradual loss of movement in the body ?
What was the <LOC>U.S.</LOC> highway death toll in 1969 ?
What kind of animals are Dorsets , Lincolns , Oxfords and Southdowns ?
What are the shortest and the longest songs ever produced ?
What letter is to the right of K on a typewriter keyboard ?
What is the origin and the meaning of the name , `` Hajo ? ''
What is the plural of gulf ?
Whose autobiography is titled Yes I Can ?
What year did the <LOC>United States</LOC> pass the Copyright law ?
What percentage of Americans own their homes ?
What 's the first day of the week ?
What city was President <PER>William McKinley</PER> shot in ?
What city has the world 's longest subway system ?
Who claimed he killed 4 , 280 buffalo as food for the crew building the <LOC>Kansas Pacific Railway</LOC> ?
What is Bombay duck ?
How many degrees cooler is the inside of a cucumber than the air outside ?
What double talking `` professor '' holds a doctorate in Nothing ?
What are the five most expensive cities in the world ?
What 19th-century writer had a country estate on the <LOC>Hudson</LOC> dubbed <LOC>Sunnyside</LOC> ?
How many layers of yellow paint is a Faber Mongol pencil lucky enough to be sprayed with ?
What is a virtual IP address ?
What was the name of the cook on Rawhide ?
What county is <LOC>Chicago</LOC> in ?
What is the wingspan of a condor ?
What facial feature typically contains about 55 hairs ?
Who was named Admiral of the Ocean Seas and Viceroy and Governor General of all the islands he might discover , and also granted 10-?? of all profits of his voyage .
How can I transport files from one computer to another ?
What 's the literary term for a play on words ?
What color were their horses ?
What does an average daycare provider get paid in <LOC>New England</LOC> ?
What author landed a 468-pound marlin without harness in the early 193 's ?
How many Americans fought for the British in the American Revolution ?
What kind of education do I need to become a flight attendant ?
What are the two languages of <LOC>Malta</LOC> ?
How many oceans are there and name them ?
What happened during the Blackhawk Indian war of 1832 ?
How many pairs of legs does a lobster have ?
What does the Latin ante mortem mean ?
What does the name Shawn mean ?
Where is the <LOC>Danube</LOC> ?
What lawyer won the largest divorce settlement , $85 million , in <LOC>U.S.</LOC> history for <PER>Sheika Dena Al-Farri</PER> ?
What do you call a group of geese ?
Who delivered his last newscast on March 6 , 1981 ?
How many times has `` Louie , Louie '' been recorded ?
How is Answers.com different from KnowPost.com ?
What is the longest place name in the <LOC>U.S.</LOC> ?
What percent liked <PER>Thatcher</PER> after she had been in power for a decade ?
Where does <PER>Buzz Aldrin</PER> want to build a permanent , manned space station ?
What was <PER>Mel Gibson</PER> 's first movie ?
Why was the <LOC>L.A.</LOC> office of <PER>Shea</PER> and <PER>Gould</PER> closed ?
How do I start a bank ?
How do Ouija Boards work ?
What horse did <PER>Zorro</PER> ride ?
How do you get a broken cork out of a bottle ?
Where can I find correct tabs for <ORG>Third Eye Blind</ORG> songs ?
How do you determine heating requirements for your home ?
What former major-league left-handed baseball pitcher was known as `` <PER>Space Man</PER> '' ?
Which hair care product told us `` hate that gray , wash it away '' ?
Why did the chicken cross the road ?
What was <PER>Michelangelo</PER> 's last name ?
Who is <PER>Barbara Jordan</PER> ?
Who was the Democratic nominee in the American presidential election ?
What was <LOC>Connecticut</LOC> 's first constitution called ?
What historical event happened in <LOC>Dogtown</LOC> in 1899 ?
What is being done about the millennium bug ?
What was the claim to fame of <PER>King Camp Gillette</PER> ?
What is the most common kind of skin cancer in the <LOC>U.S.</LOC> ?
What is Olestra ?
What Asian country has a bill of rights for cows ?
How many fingers are used to draw a bow ?
What are two plants that clothes are made from ?
When was Hurricane Hugo ?
What is the most heavily caffeinated soft drink ?
What President-to-be was the first member of <ORG>Congress</ORG> to enlist following the attack on <LOC>Pearl Harbor</LOC> ?
What was the price of <ORG>Varian Associates</ORG> ' vacuum products division ?
When was `` the Great Depression '' ?
What language is mostly spoken in <LOC>Brazil</LOC> ?
What college produced the most winning Super Bowl quarterbacks ?
How do you solve `` Rubik 's Cube '' ?
What is prepared mustard ?
What classical Spanish writer warned : `` All that glitters is not gold '' ?
What does `` antidisestablishmentarianism '' mean ?
What actor married <PER>John F. Kennedy</PER> 's sister ?
What does a topophobic actor suffer from ?
Who fired <PER>Maria Ybarra</PER> from her position in <ORG>San Diego council</ORG> ?
The italian artist , <PER>Maurizio Pellegrin</PER> , is how old ?
What type of hunting are retrievers used for ?
What is <PER>Colin Powell</PER> best known for ?
Who was the first black golfer to tee off in the Masters ?
What city is the setting for <PER>Puccini</PER> 's opera La Boheme ?
What <LOC>U.S.</LOC> President showed a fondness for munching on bee pollen bars ?
What is measured in curies ?
Whose cover is that of an employee of <ORG>Universal Import and Export</ORG> ?
What former president 's daughter has written a book titled Murder in the White House ?
What fictional character is known as the `` <PER>melancholy Dane</PER> '' ?
<LOC>Italy</LOC> is the largest producer of what ?
What longtime game show host dropped dead while jogging in <LOC>Central Park</LOC> in 1984 ?
What is the meaning of <PER>W.B. Yeat</PER> 's poem , `` The Three Hermits ? ''
Who were the `` filthiest people alive ? ''
What infectious disease is the world 's deadliest ?
What is Spumante ?
What is an isthmus ?
What was the name of the orca that died of a fungal infection ?
Where is <LOC>Mozambique</LOC> located ?
What is <LOC>Mississippi</LOC> 's state animal ?
What 's the origin of the word ` news ' ?
What did <PER>Dan Aykroyd</PER> and <PER>John Belushi</PER> quit Saturday Night Live to become ?
How many months does a normal human pregnancy last ?
How do fuel injectors work ?
How can your school march in the Macy 's Thanksgiving Parade ?
What is the real name of disc jockey `` <PER>Wolfman Jack</PER> '' ?
What Italian liner was hijacked in 1985 ?
What city houses the <LOC>U.S.</LOC> headquarters of <ORG>Procter and Gamble</ORG> ?
What soap was touted as being `` for people who like people '' ?
How much was the minimum wage in 1991 ?
What does NAFTA stand for ?
Who invented silly putty ?
What new middle school was built in <LOC>Philadelphia</LOC> , <LOC>Pennsylvania</LOC> last year ?
Who patented the first phonograph ?
What are some tips for building a fire in a fireplace ?
What do manatees eat ?
How do you say 2 in Latin ?
What were popular songs and types of songs in the 1920s ?
How many Vietnamese were there in the <LOC>Soviet Union</LOC> ?
What is November 's birthstone ?
What is a Certified Nurse Midwife ?
On average , how many miles are there to the <LOC>moon</LOC> ?
Who created private detective <PER>Philip Marlowe</PER> ?
What <PER>Boris Pasternak</PER> book sold 5 , 0 copies to become the fiction best-seller of 1958 ?
What is the origin of the expression `` tout de suite '' ?
What is the longest English word ?
What is the purpose of a car bra ?
What is <PER>D.B. Cooper</PER> known for ?
Who is <PER>Colin Powell</PER> ?
What species is a colt ?
What is the full name of the PLO ?
What is the smallest country in <LOC>Africa</LOC> ?
Who coined the term NN cyberspace `` in his novel NN Neuromancer '' ?
What age followed the Bronze Age ?
What is her profession ?
What is the full name of the man who invented the multicolored game cube that has 42.3 quintillion potential combinations ?
What does the word LASER mean ?
What does the name `` Anthony '' mean ?
Who was <PER>Lauren Bacall</PER> 's first husband ?
What is a rhomboideus minor ?
How many hands does <PER>Bjorn Borg</PER> use when hitting his forehand ?
How many people died on D-Day ?
What <LOC>U.S.</LOC> Congressman said : `` Keep the faith , baby '' .
Who created the character of <PER>Scrooge</PER> ?
Where is <LOC>Windsor Castle</LOC> ?
When did the Dow first reach ?
Why were people recruited for the Vietnam War ?
What party was <PER>Winston Churchill</PER> a member of ?
What American League baseball team 's worst finish between 1926 and 1964 was fourth ?
Where can I find the names of all the 15 Pokemon ?
What state does <PER>Martha Stewart</PER> live in ?
Which killer whale died at <ORG>Sea World</ORG> of a fungal infection ?
What are the <ORG>Benelux</ORG> countries ?
Where 's the <LOC>Petrified Forest</LOC> ?
What is a language spoken by the Sioux ?
Where is <LOC>Tornado Alley</LOC> ?
Who was the author of `` John Brown 's Body '' ?
What American poet wrote : `` Good fences make good neighbors '' ?
What state in the <LOC>U.S.</LOC> has the most blacks ?
Why are electric cars less efficient in the northeast than in <LOC>California</LOC> ?
What was the occupation of <PER>Mandy Rice-Davies</PER> ?
What is the city in which <PER>Maurizio Pellegrin</PER> lives called ?
Who painted the <LOC>Sistine Chapel</LOC> ?
Name the various costumed personas of Dr. <PER>Henry Pym</PER> .
What breed of dog was the `` Little Rascals '' dog ?
What are the living conditions in <LOC>Cuba</LOC> ?
What color are school buses ?
What is the oldest website on the Internet ?
What events happened January 26 , 1978 ?
What explorers followed <PER>Columbus</PER> to the <LOC>Americas</LOC> ?
Who is actress <PER>Goldie Hawn</PER> 's current actor boyfriend ?
Who banned <PER>Peter Rose</PER> from baseball for betting on games ?
What are the seven virtues ?
What other name were the `` Little Rascals '' known as ?
When was the <LOC>San Francisco</LOC> fire ?
What is a fear of food ?
How many casinos are in <LOC>Atlantic City</LOC> , <LOC>NJ</LOC> ?
What year did the Vietnam War end ?
What are the names of <PER>Richard Nixon</PER> 's two daughters ?
What 's the word for broken glass or sharp rocks embedded in cement on top of a wall ?
What is the chromosome number of an elephant ?
What organization was founded by the Rev. <PER>Jerry Falwell</PER> ?
What 's the longest river in the world ?
Which soft drink does <PER>Madonna</PER> advertise for ?
What company is being bought by <ORG>Yahoo</ORG> and how much is the deal worth ?
When was <LOC>Berlin</LOC> 's <LOC>Brandenburg gate</LOC> erected ?
How many double-word-score spaces are there on a Scrabble Crossword Game board ?
What mountain range is traversed by the highest railroad in the world ?
Why were the American soldiers in WWI called `` Doughboys ''
Who was nicknamed <PER>The Little Corporal</PER> ?
How many CDs has <PER>Garth Brooks</PER> sold ?
Name the vessel used by the <ORG>Atari Force</ORG> in the <ORG>DC</ORG> comics .
Where are the leading medical groups specializing in lung diseases ?
How can I find online spelling , and punctuation drills for my 6th grader ?
What 's the sacred river of <LOC>India</LOC> ?
What is <PER>Stefan Edberg</PER> 's native country ?
What is the only gland in humans that can regenerate itself ?
How many Gutenberg Bibles are there ?
What astronomical phenomenon takes place in Jan. 1999 ?
What information can you get me on <LOC>Fairground Park</LOC> in <LOC>St. Louis</LOC>
What was American folk hero <PER>John Chapman</PER> 's nickname ?
What is the difference between a median and a mean ?
What was the top box office movie in April 1998 ?
What makes thunder ?
What author did photographer <PER>Yousuf Karsh</PER> call `` the shiest man I ever met '' ?
Which is the largest clock , diameter wise , in <LOC>Europe</LOC> ?
What plant is rum made from ?
What country are Godiva chocolates from ?
Name the poet of the poem which begins : I do not know much about gods ; but I think that the river Is a strong brown god-sullen , and untamed ?
Which condiment was once sold as a patent medicine ?
What <LOC>U.S.</LOC> state records the least rainfall ?
Why did the world enter a global depression in 1929 ?
What was archy , and mehitabel ?
What <LOC>Texas</LOC> city got its name from the Spanish for `` yellow '' ?
What are the chemicals used in glowsticks ?
What country did the <LOC>Nile River</LOC> originate in ?
What color are tennis balls ?
What barroom judge called himself <PER>The Law West of the Pecos</PER> ?
What excuse did the <ORG>NATO</ORG> people give for hitting the Chinese embassy ?
Who was President of <LOC>Costa Rica</LOC> in 1994 ?
What sports event is <PER>Meyer Wolfsheim</PER> supposed to have fixed in The Great Gatsby ?
What country has the best defensive position in the board game Diplomacy ?
What two countries share the <LOC>Khyber Pass</LOC> ?
Who was chairman of the <ORG>Senate select committee</ORG> that tried to get to the bottom of Watergate ?
What is the origin of the surname of Braun ?
What card game has variations called Canfield , Klondike and Spider ?
What is Australia Day ?
What mammal of <LOC>North America</LOC> is the world 's longest-lived for its size ?
What was the Chivington Massacre ?
What actor starred in 1980 's Blue Lagoon , 1982 's The Pirate Movie and 1983 's A Night in Heaven ?
How many home runs did <PER>Lou Gehrig</PER> have during his career ?
In what city is the headquarters of <ORG>Sinn Fein</ORG> ?
Where can I find information on <PER>George Bush</PER> ?
Who is the voice of Miss <PER>Piggy</PER> ?
What is the dialogue circle in cartoons called ?
What does the word camaro mean , from the <ORG>GM</ORG> car the Camaro ?
Who replaced <PER>Bert Parks</PER> as the host of The Miss America Pageant ?
How many boys play the game in <PER>Winslow Homer</PER> 's 1872 painting Snap the Whip ?
What is the AIM-54C Phoenix ?
When are sheep shorn ?
What sport is <PER>Chris Jogis</PER> a top player of ?
What 's the second-largest island in the world ?
What is the definition of low island ?
What century does Captain <PER>Video</PER> live in ?
What types of water pollution are there ?
How many astronauts manned each Project Mercury flight ?
What soft drink would provide me with the biggest intake of caffeine ?
What 's the name of a golf course in <LOC>Myrtle Beach</LOC> ?
What are some of the significant historical events of the 1990s ?
Name the only extant trilogy of classical Greek plays .
Where is <LOC>Logan Airport</LOC> ?
What is the difference between Neoclassical art and Romanticism art ?
Who was the first person inducted into the <LOC>U.S.</LOC> Swimming Hall of Fame ?
What golfer has been called <PER>Ohio Fats</PER> and <PER>Blobbo</PER> ?
Who murdered <PER>Leno</PER> and <PER>Rosemary LaBianca</PER> on August 1
What is the average cost for four years of medical school ?
What does <PER>God</PER> create in the first sentence of the Bible ?
Which of the following men was not married to <PER>Rita Hayworth</PER> ?
What is the current ticket fare from <LOC>Cairo</LOC> to <LOC>Barbados</LOC> ?
What does NN O `` mean when used as a prefix in Irish surnames ?
How do you find oxidation numbers ?
What is the state nickname of <LOC>Mississippi</LOC> ?
What is <LOC>Black Hills</LOC> , <LOC>South Dakota</LOC> most famous for ?
What 1966 boob tube bomb took astronauts back to prehistoric times ?
How many students attend the <ORG>University of Massachusetts</ORG> ?
Who said , `` I shall return . '' during World War Two ?
What holidays are celebrated in <LOC>Ireland</LOC> ?
Who portrayed <PER>Etta Place</PER> , companion to <PER>Butch Cassidey</PER> and the <PER>Sundance Kid</PER> ?
What are the Greek numerals ?
What 's the name of the temple that is located near the capital city of <LOC>Laos</LOC> ?
What is a fear of sleep ?
What auto race was <PER>Wilbur Reed</PER> the first to win three times ?
What are the most common breeding birds in the <LOC>U.S.</LOC> ?
What was organized as a Confederate veterans ' social club in <LOC>Pulaski</LOC> , in <LOC>Tennessee</LOC> , in 1866 ?
How do you look up criminal records on the Internet ?
Where is the actress , <PER>Marion Davies</PER> , buried ?
What is an example of an actual case of using the Fourteenth Amendment ?
Who was the Charlie perfume woman ?
Who portrayed `` <PER>Rosanne Rosanna-Dana</PER> '' on the television show `` Saturday Night Live '' ?
What singer became despondent over the death of <PER>Freddie Prinze</PER> , quit show business , and then quit the business ?
When did Iraqi troops invade <LOC>Kuwait</LOC> ?
What was <PER>Mark Johnson</PER> referring to when he said : `` I still can 't believe it- we beat the Russians ? ''
What car was driven in the 199 release of `` Smokey and the Bandit '' ?
What was the backup singing group for <PER>Roy Rogers</PER> ?
What famous singing cowboy owns the <ORG>California Angels</ORG> baseball team ?
What 1915 film was the first to gross $5 million ?
Where did the term `` 86 '' come from ?
What causes someone to be ticklish ?
What is the probability that at least 2 out of 25 people will have the same birthday ?
How many Canadians emmigrate each year ?
Why did several <LOC>San Diego</LOC> schools remove apples from students menus ?
What musical instrument did <PER>Sherlock Holmes</PER> play ?
Who was <PER>Gerald Ford</PER> 's vice president ?
What is `` the washed vodka '' ?
How many different languages are spoken in <LOC>Europe</LOC> ?
What year was <PER>Desmond Mpilo Tutu</PER> awarded the Nobel Peace Prize ?
What 's a `` Drinker respirator '' better known as ?
Who invented batteries ?
Why do recipe books recommend starting with cold water when you boil something ?
Where can I buy a good snowboard for less than $200 ?
What title did <PER>Suzette Charles</PER> assume for two months in 1984 ?
What was the infamous pseudonym of <PER>Peter Sutcliffe</PER> ?
What is <PER>Smokey The Bear</PER> 's middle name ?
What is <PER>Nicholas Cage</PER> 's occupation ?
What British TV series featured <PER>Emma Peel</PER> ?
What <LOC>London</LOC> street is the home of British journalism ?
What tragedy befell the city of <LOC>Dogtown</LOC> in 1899 ?
What is the Immaculate Conception ?
What are the names of all the <ORG>U.S. Navy</ORG> aircraft carriers ?
What format was VHS 's main competition ?
What is Candlemas Day ?
In what city is the famed <LOC>St. Mark 's Square</LOC> ?
What does the <ORG>Ouarterly Review of Doublespeak</ORG> call an `` inoperative statement '' ?
How much did the minimum wage amount to in 1991 ?
Where is <ORG>Tufts University</ORG> ?
What is a pyrotechnic display ?
How do I find out about jobs ?
What Japanese manufacturer is known for both its pianos and its motorcycles ?
What is the chemical reactivity of argon ?
How many engines does a <ORG>Boeing</ORG> 737 have ?
What is the origin of the term `` The Brooklyn Side '' in bowling ?
What is a fear of being cold ?
How long was <PER>Mao</PER> 's 1930s Long March ?
What net game sees its women 's world amateur champions receive the Uber Cup ?
What four-legged creature did a <ORG>Cornell University</ORG> study say would make man 's best companion in space ?
What does a teaspoon of matter weigh in a black hole ?
What did British companies stick 175 , 0 tons of tea into in 1982 ?
What province is <LOC>Edmonton</LOC> located in ?
How can I find out how much income tax is paid on Social Security income on the 1998 income tax ?
Who did <PER>Sonny Liston</PER> succeed as world heavyweight boxing champion ?
What is <LOC>California</LOC> 's state bird ?
What is <PER>Martin Luther King Jr.</PER> 's real birthday ?
Name the various super-teams to which <PER>the Angel</PER> has belonged .
How does <PER>Zatanna</PER> perform her magic in <ORG>DC</ORG> comics ?
What 's the name of <PER>Jacques Cousteau</PER> 's research ship ?
What President dispatched a cruiser to carry <PER>Charles Lindbergh</PER> home after his epic flight ?
Whose video is titled Shape Up with Arnold ?
In which <PER>Kevin Costner</PER> movie did Sioux Indians play a role ?
How many <PER>James Bond</PER> novels are there ?
How do you get dates with the `` <ORG>Hooters</ORG> '' girls ?
What bird can swim but can 't fly ?
How can I get a comic character I made copyrighted and published ?
How large is the <LOC>Arctic refuge</LOC> to preserve unique wildlife and wilderness value on <LOC>Alaska</LOC> 's north coast ?
What is Plc ?
How much electricity does the brain need to work ?
How many acres in a mile ?
What <PER>Dickens</PER> novel has <PER>David</PER> carrying the message `` Barkis is willin '' to <PER>Peggy</PER> ?
What is a hyperlink ?
Who 's the twin brother of the Greek goddess <PER>Artemis</PER> ?
Where did marijuana come from ?
What is the per-capita income of <LOC>Colombia</LOC> , <LOC>South America</LOC> , ?
What novel has <PER>Big Brother</PER> watching ?
How many Grammys did <PER>Michael Jackson</PER> win in 1983 ?
What does Elysium mean ?
What is the oldest website on the Internet ?
What is Shalom ?
What was the favorite sport of <PER>Tom Wolfe</PER> 's The Pump House Gang ?
What organic fuel do bog-dwellers use a `` slane '' to cut ?
What is the average age of a member of the team that worked on the Manhatten Project ?
What country received all the Nobel Prizes awarded in 1976 ?
How do you get rid on woodpeckers ?
How many syllables are there in a line of hendecasyllabic poetry ?
What soft drink first appeared in the <LOC>Old Corner Drug Store</LOC> in <LOC>Waco</LOC> , <LOC>Texas</LOC> , in 1885 ?
What is <LOC>Britain</LOC> 's possession on the Chinese mainland ?
Who was <LOC>America</LOC> 's first Public Enemy No. 1 ?
How many children under 18 are victims of some sort of Physical Abuse each year ?
What is the origin of thank you notes ?
What did <PER>Jimmy Stewart</PER> invent ?
What generation am I in ?
What is a fear of hell ?
Who is <PER>Dear Abby</PER> ?
Who lives at <LOC>24 Sussex Drive</LOC> , <LOC>Ottawa</LOC> ?
What is Jell-O made from ?
Who was <PER>Monet</PER> ?
What are the only two states that incorporate the Confederate battle flag in their flags ?
How do you make panoramic sugar eggs for Easter - the ones with the scene inside ?
What 's the Southern dish made of pigs ' small intestines ?
Where is <LOC>Guam</LOC> ?
Who was the famous door-to-door brush salesman ?
What is the executor in a will ?
What inescapable purveyor of background music celebrated its 5th anniversary in July , 1984 ?
How many people in <LOC>America</LOC> snore ?
Who is always trying to get the rent from <PER>Andy Capp</PER> ?
What soft drink is most heavily caffeinated ?
Who did <PER>Jackie Kennedy</PER> commission to write The Death of a President ?
Which drug is commonly used to treat AIDS ?
How many stars are there on the <LOC>Soviet Union</LOC> 's flag ?
What is the difference between microprocessors & microcontrollers ?
Who sought to create The Great Society ?
What are tourist attractions in <LOC>Reims</LOC> ?
What are the lengths of pearl necklaces ?
Who said : `` Soldiers win the battles and generals get the credit '' ?
What is the proof that houseplants metabolize carcinogens ?
What prompted the co-pilot of the Enola Gay to enter only `` My God '' in his log ?
How long does it take the typical hen to lay 19 dozen eggs ?
What <LOC>Colorado</LOC> city owns its own glacier ?
What is the history of `` the toast '' ?
What was the name of the Protestant revolt against the supremacy of the Pope ?
What is an arab strap ?
How much does it cost , average or whatever is available , to produce and send junk mail catalogues in the <LOC>US</LOC> ? , DT CD NN NN ,
Who is the current <ORG>UN</ORG> Secretary General ?
Who provides telephone service in <LOC>Orange County</LOC> , <LOC>California</LOC> ?
Where did guinea pigs originate ?
What two countries ' coastlines border the <LOC>Bay of Biscay</LOC> ?
Why did Egyptians shave their eyebrows ?
What organization did Mr. <PER>Waverly</PER> assign agents for ?
When was the slinky invented ?
What are the characters ' names in the Scooby-Doo cartoon ?
What is a fear of cold ?
What was <PER>Eduard Shevardnadze</PER> 's job in the <LOC>Soviet Union</LOC> ?
What causes rust ?
Which is the only <PER>Dick Tracy</PER> villain to appear three times ?
What was the monster in <PER>Spielberg</PER> 's film `` Jaws '' ?
What color is an Arctic fox in winter ?
What do the names Neil , Mary , and Anthony mean ?
What European capital celebrated its 2 , 000th anniversary in 1951 ?
Why do people in the upper peninsula of <LOC>Michagin</LOC> say `` eh ? '' ?
What flower did <PER>Vincent Van Gogh</PER> paint ?
What country was the setting of You Only Live Twice ?
What was <PER>Thatcher</PER> 's approval rating after 10 years in power ?
<PER>Winnie the Pooh</PER> is what kind of animal ?
What was the first <ORG>Funk 'N Lata</ORG> , Brazilian group , success ?
What is a handheld PC ?
What did <PER>John Hinckley</PER> do to impress <PER>Jodie Foster</PER> ?
What is <PER>Larry King</PER> 's job ?
How many calories are in a tomato ?
In what state was the first co-educational college established
What war saw a naval battle between the luxury liners Cap Trafalgar and the Carmania ?
What is the treatment for depression ?
What is a fear of slime ?
What country in <LOC>Latin America</LOC> is the largest one ?
On which Hawaiian island is <LOC>Pearl Harbor</LOC> ?
What feathered cartoon characters do Yugoslavians know as <PER>Vlaja</PER> , <PER>Gaja</PER> , and <PER>Raja</PER> ?
What <PER>Marx</PER> Brothers movie centers on a stolen painting ?
What was unusual about <PER>Alexandra</PER> 's appearance in Josie and the Pussycats ?
What is the origin of the word `` mind '' ?
When was <PER>Dick Clark</PER> born ?
What game is fatal to anybody over 21 ?
What is the death toll of people dying from tuberculosis ?
What happened to <PER>Moon Maiden</PER> ?
What city is wiener schnitzel named for ?
What are the <LOC>Urals</LOC> ?
How can you stop the itch from poison ivy ?
What desert has the highest sand dunes ?
What two countries contain <LOC>Sierra Nevada mountains</LOC> ?
How do you tell your parents you are dating an older man ?
How long was the TV mission of Star Trek 's Enterprise to be ?
What phone number can I call to have a tree planted ?
When did the `` Star-Spangled Banner '' become the national anthem ?
Who was <PER>Lacan</PER> ?
What are the four natural aids used in riding a horse ?
What continent 's name appears on the upper left corner of a Budweiser label ?
Who was the Secretary of War in the Civil War during the Battle of Gettysburg ?
Who did <PER>Bobby Fischer</PER> beat to win the world chess championship ?
How do you exterminate bees that are in the walls of your home ? Will bee eggs remain over winter ?
Where can I get information and statistics on countries and nations ?
Name a Gaelic language .
What day is August 13 , 1971 ?
Where can I find a list of all the companies in <LOC>America</LOC> that offer a direct stock purchase plan ?
How do you send a movie transcript to Hollywood so that it can be produced into a film ?
What literary classic centers on the search for a treasure in gold worth 7 , 0 pounds ?
What is the origin of blue for boys and pink for girls ?
What is the name of the <PER>Michelangelo</PER> painting that shows two hands with fingers touching ?
How big is a quart ?
What is the Hub of <LOC>London</LOC> ?
<PER>Jude Law</PER> acted in which film ?
What causes panic attacks ?
What was the filling in the first golf balls ?
What drug did <PER>Sigmund Freud</PER> become fascinated with while experimenting with the treatment of neurasthenia ?
What country was A Terrible Beauty to <PER>Leon Uris</PER> ?
What is typhoid fever ?
Where can I buy a hat like the kind <PER>Jay Kay</PER> from <ORG>Jamiroquai</ORG> wears ?
What are the Twin Cities ?
What is <PER>Beethoven</PER> 's 9th symphony called ?
Name the lawyer for <PER>Randy Craft</PER> .
Which breakfast cereal brought you `` the best each morning '' ?
What does Ms. , Miss , and Mrs. stand for ?
What is the <ORG>Homelite Inc.</ORG> home page ?
What explosive do you get by mixing charcoal , sulfur and saltpeter ?
What mountainous region of the world is the Lhasa Apso dog native to ?
What cancer is commonly associated with AIDS ?
How long does it take light to reach the <LOC>Earth</LOC> from the <LOC>Sun</LOC> ?
Who lives at <LOC>39 Stone Canyon Way</LOC> ?
How many questions are on this thing ?
Who played <PER>Humpty Dumpty</PER> in the 1933 film Alice in Wonderland ?
Who is <PER>Karenna Gore</PER> , <PER>Al Gore</PER> 's oldest daughter , married to ?
Who played the title role in I Was a Teenage Werewolf ?
Why are there olives in martinis ?
In what year did <PER>Hitler</PER> gain power of <LOC>Germany</LOC> ?
What year did <PER>Rossetti</PER> paint `` Beata Beatrix '' ?
What record company produced the 1978 movie The Wiz ?
Where can I find information about touring the <LOC>Philippines</LOC> ?
What did <ORG>The Gas House Gang</ORG> play ?
How many square feet is <PER>Bill Gates</PER> ' home ?
What is the name of actor <PER>Rex Harrison</PER> 's son , who starred in a modestly popular TV show during the late 1960's ?
What is the highest Roman numeral ?
What 's the most popular form of bridge ?
Who was the inventor of the stove ?
What comedian has a legendary reputation for stealing jokes ?
Where can I find information on the cyclone that hit <LOC>New Jersey</LOC> on 8/28/1941 ?
Boxing Day is celebrated on what date ?
What are the first ten amendements passed ?
What is another term for the painful wrist syndrome ?
How is the new <ORG>Ford</ORG> Econoline van F25 V1 engine ?
Who was the king who was forced to agree to the Magna Carta ?
Who was made the first honorary citizen of the <LOC>U.S.</LOC> ?
What game is <PER>Garry Kasparov</PER> really good at ?
Where was <PER>Richard Nixon</PER> when <PER>Gerald Ford</PER> became president ?
Where does the <LOC>U.S.</LOC> rank among world countries in area ?
What novel did <PER>Ian Fleming</PER> introduce <PER>James Bond</PER> in ?
What was the target rate for M3 growth in 1992 ?
What baseball team was routinely called `` <ORG>dem bums</ORG> '' by its frustrated fans ?
Name of scholar on whose literal translations from the Chinese and Japanese <PER>Ezra Pound</PER> depended ?
When did <LOC>Israel</LOC> begin turning the <LOC>Gaza Strip</LOC> and <LOC>Jericho</LOC> over to the <ORG>PLO</ORG> ?
What are the major differences in the <ORG>Catholic</ORG> and <ORG>Methodist religions</ORG> ?
Name the On Stage character whose face was never seen .
How much energy is released when oxygen and hydrogen mix ?
What is the best Internet business to go into ?
What does Venus Retrograde mean ?
Who is known as `` the world 's oldest teenager '' ?
What are the largest breweries in the world ?
What does Las Vegas mean ?
What does the word `` meta '' mean ?
What keeps clouds in the air ?
What 's the term for any four-sided figure ?
<PER>Ray Charles</PER> plays which instrument ?
What country and western singer is known as <PER>The Silver Fox</PER> ?
What building appropriately enough is depicted on the back of the 1-dollar bill ?
What is graduate school ?
What is the difference between <LOC>New York</LOC>-style and <LOC>Chicago</LOC>-style pizza ?
What baseball team owner and sailor is known as <PER>The Mouth of the South</PER> ?
What type of betting is used in horse racing ?
What kind of hat does <PER>Bat Masterson</PER> wear ?
Who was with <PER>Patricia Hearst</PER> the night she was kidnaped ?
What is the <PER>Viking Prince</PER> 's first name ?
What does the abbreviation cwt. ?
In what deodorant commercial did tenants have adjoining medicine cabinets ?
Where is <ORG>Rider College</ORG> located ?
What boxer 's life story is titled Raging Bull ?
For what reason did some <LOC>San Diego</LOC> schools stop serving apples ?
Who advised listeners to `` see the U.S.A. in your Chevrolet '' ?
Where was the first restaurant ?
Where can I find full written draft of CTBT ?
How many horses died during the civil war ?
How much waste does an average dairy cow produce in a day ?
What Nobel laureate was expelled from the <LOC>Philippines</LOC> before the conference on <LOC>East Timor</LOC> ?
What woman has carried the most multiple births , twins , triplets , etc. , ?
How many minutes were there on the original GE College Bowl clock ?
What is the average time it takes for a male to ejaculate ?
What is website of the <ORG>International Court of Justice</ORG> ?
Where are 8 of the 10 highest mountains in the world ?
Where can I look at a perpetual calendar ?
How many astronauts have been on the <LOC>moon</LOC> ?
In what year did the Bounty mutiny happen ?
What is the only substance that gives food its `` taste '' when eaten ?
How do you reference a website ?
What is pandoro ?
What do the letters ZIP stand for in the phrase `` ZIP code '' ?
Which Bourbon king was restored to the French throne during <PER>Napoleon</PER> 's abdication ?
What is one of the cities that the <ORG>University of Minnesota</ORG> is located in ?
What are the words to `` My Way '' written by <PER>Paul Anka</PER> ?
How do I install a tile floor ?
What is the quickest and easiest way to get nail polish out of clothes ?
Why was the zipper invented ?
What 's the No. 1 killer in industrialized countries ?
Name four famous cartoon cats .
What daughter of <PER>Henry VIII</PER> and <PER>Anne Boleyn</PER> became queen of <LOC>England</LOC> ?
How did ` stat ' come to be used as an expression for quickly ?
What 's the most common nickname of <LOC>U.S.</LOC> college football teams ?
What 's the distinction of <ORG>U.S. Supreme Court</ORG> Justice Thurgood Marshall ?
What is the most useful site on the Internet ?
What is the world 's highest peak ?
What was a Mae West on a World War II battleship ?
Define cosmology .
What comedienne upstaged <PER>Dwight D. Eisenhower</PER> 's first inauguration by giving birth to her first child ?
What are amicable numbers ?
When were the Olympic Games in which <PER>Nadia Comaneci</PER> became popular played ?
Where is <LOC>Hearst Castle</LOC> , built by publisher <PER>William Randolph Hearst</PER> ?
What 's the largest <LOC>U.S.</LOC> city on the <LOC>Great Lakes</LOC> ?
Who sang about <PER>Desmond</PER> and <PER>Molly Jones</PER> ?
What magazine gives us the cream , not the skim ?
What does the technique called `` cold fusion '' produce ?
What costume designer decided that <PER>Michael Jackson</PER> should only wear one glove ?
What meter did <PER>Shakespeare</PER> use in writing : `` To be , or not to be , that is the question.. . '' ?
How many rows of sprocket holes does a roll of 35-millimeter film have ?
What is the goat population of the world ?
What company was the original sponsor of TV 's Superman ?
What term does a Czech use to describe a Pole ?
What sea separates <LOC>Naples</LOC> and <LOC>Algiers</LOC> ?
How many lawyers are there in the <LOC>state of New Jersey</LOC> ?
What are the most common elements in seawater ?
Describe the Finnish music personality <PER>Salonen</PER> 's appearance .
What is the origin of the ethnic category `` caucasian '' ?
What is a stratocaster ?
What kind of science is cosmology ?
Name the blind sculptress in love with the <ORG>Fantastic Four</ORG> 's <PER>Thing</PER> .
What 's the second-lightest element ?
What do you call a `` twirl '' in ballet ?
What is the brand name of daminozide ?
What is the former name of <LOC>Zimbabwe</LOC> ?
What <ORG>National Basketball Association</ORG> superstar told his story in Giant Steps ?
What animals did <ORG>The Amazing Three</ORG> masquerade as ?
How did the bikini bathing suite get its name ?
When did <PER>Fraze</PER> get his first patent for the pull-tab can ?
How many games are played in a five-team round-robin tournament ?
Who developed the first polio vaccine ?
Who made the first gas engine ?
What country claimed <PER>Rubens</PER> , <PER>Van Dyck</PER> and <PER>Bruegel</PER> as citizens ?
What civil war was fought between 1936 and 1939 ?
How many questions do you have on your database ?
How do clouds form ?
What character did <PER>Tex Avery</PER> first create upon arriving at <ORG>MGM</ORG> ?
When was the <ORG>Triangle Shirtwaist</ORG> fire ?
What Asian spiritual and political leader was married at the age of 13 ?
Where is <LOC>Ocho Rios</LOC> ?
What is the half-life of P-32 ?
What ocean does <LOC>Mauritania</LOC> border ?
Why do pressure cookers save time in the kitchen ?
Why are there 12 people on a jury in criminal cases ?
What do <ORG>Christian Scientists</ORG> believe in ?
What World War I battle saw 6 , 0 troops killed in one day ?
What country is <LOC>Kosovo</LOC> a part of ?
Tell me what city the <LOC>Kentucky Horse Park</LOC> is near ?
What computer operating system is on the most computers ?
What is <PER>Bill Gross</PER> 's email address ?
What is the economic impact of unemployment on the economy ?
What do the letters D.C. stand for in <LOC>Washington , D.C.</LOC> ?
What animals can live the longest without food ?
What English queen had seventeen children ?
What is the approximate population of <LOC>Las Vegas</LOC> , <LOC>N.M</LOC> ?
How much does the President get paid ?
What two baseball players make up the battery ?
What 's the largest letter in <PER>Salvador Dali</PER> 's signature ?
What does an irate car owner call iron oxide ?
Of children between the ages of two and eleven , what percentage watch `` The Simpsons '' ?
What 's the northernmost <LOC>U.S.</LOC> state apart from <LOC>Alaska</LOC> ?
Name an art gallery in <LOC>New York</LOC> .
Who sells Viagra ?
What musical instrument did <PER>Prewitt</PER> play in <PER>James Jones</PER> 's From Here to Eternity ?
What is the Home Rule Act ?
What building are British monarchs crowned in ?
What are Bellworts ?
Who was <PER>Darius</PER> ?
What movie told of <PER>Anna Anderson</PER> 's claim to be a Russian czar 's daughter ?
Who did <PER>Dita Beard</PER> work for ?
What kind of creature is a coot ?
What country was first to use the airplane as a weapon of war , against the Turks in <LOC>Libya</LOC> ?
What university was <PER>Woodrow Wilson</PER> President of ?
What is a fear of disease ?
What kind of meat is Fray Bentos synonymous with ?
What did Mr. <PER>Magoo</PER> flog on TV for <ORG>General Electric</ORG> ?
What are the words to the Canadian National anthem ?
What is the name of the Jewish alphabet ?
Who served as inspiration for the schoolteacher portrayed by <PER>Robin Williams</PER> in `` Dead Poets Society '' ?
What is <ORG>Columbia Tristar</ORG> 's phone number ?
Which one of the original seven Mercury program astronauts did not fly on any of the Mercury flights ?
Who is the best known villain of the 165 Gunpowder Plot ?
What is the capital of <LOC>Burkina Faso</LOC> ?
What continent is <LOC>Bolivia</LOC> on ?
Why was <PER>Muhammad Ali</PER> stripped of his title and barred from boxing in 1967 ?
Who killed more people , <PER>Hitler</PER> or <PER>Stalin</PER> ?
What caused <ORG>Shea & Gould</ORG> to close their <LOC>L.A.</LOC> office ?
What 's the only mammal that can 't jump ?
What <LOC>U.S.</LOC> state has the most blondes ?
What war saw battles at <LOC>Parrot 's Beak</LOC> and <LOC>Black Virgin</LOC> ?
What was the <LOC>U.S.</LOC> highway death toll in 1969 ?
What does the name Kelly mean ?
What is a phalanx ?
What mustachioed comedian portrayed <PER>Frankie</PER> in North to Alaska ?
What does each of the utilities cost in Monopoly ?
What actor and World War II airman had a $5 , 0 bounty put on his head by <PER>Hermann Goering</PER> ?
What does e.g. stand for ?
What is the name of the medical condition in which a baby is born without a brain ?
How do storms form ?
Who is <PER>Nicolo Paganini</PER> ?
What city is often called <LOC>The Insurance Capital of the World</LOC> ?
What are the three animals in <PER>Sheila Burnford</PER> 's The Incredible Journey ?
Who portrayed <PER>Dracula</PER> in <ORG>Hammer Studios</ORG> ' films ?
When were fish first believed to be found on <LOC>earth</LOC> ?
What President 's favorite Biblical quotation was : `` Come now , and let us reason together '' .
How many elevators do you ride to reach the top floor of the <LOC>Empire State Building</LOC> ?
Name the food company that traveled to <PER>Soviet Georgia</PER> to film a series of ads .
What country was Sir <PER>Edmund Hillary</PER> born in ?
What 's an infant seal called ?
What was the proper Laugh-In respones to : `` Say goodnight , Dick '' ?
What city was <PER>John F. Kennedy</PER> nominated for president in ?
How long does a dog sleep ?
What 1963 <PER>Joseph L. Mankiewicz</PER> film cost $28 million ?
What Japanese electronics company was named for a coastal city northeast of <LOC>Tokyo</LOC> ?
What can you be fined for having a dog on a beach ?
Where did the Battle of the Bulge take place ?
How much will the <LOC>California</LOC> be in the year 2000 ?
What mystery writer penned `` ...the glory that was Greece , and the grandeur that was Rome '' ?
What state full of milk and honey was the destination in The Grapes of Wrath ?
What is the tallest building in <LOC>Japan</LOC> ?
Where is <ORG>Sinn Fein</ORG> 's headquarters ?
Name <PER>Li 'l Abner</PER> 's favorite Indian drink .
What are some important events of the 1830 's ?
The Iraqis launched their attack on <LOC>Kuwait</LOC> on what day ?
What letter adorns the flag of <LOC>Rwanda</LOC> ?
What did 8 , CD NNS VBP TO VB NNP POS NN .
What is <PER>God</PER> ?
What country 's northernmost city is <LOC>Darwin</LOC> ?
What sound does <LOC>Olympia</LOC> , <LOC>Washington</LOC> , overlook ?
What TV show chronicled the lives of <PER>Katy Holstrum</PER> and Congressman <PER>Glen Morley</PER> ?
What <LOC>Kentucky</LOC> city calls itself <LOC>The Horse Center of America</LOC> ?
How many penny-farthings are there on a Trivial Pursuit game board ?
What 's the most abundant element in the <LOC>sun</LOC> ?
What European country boasts the city of <LOC>Furth</LOC> , found where the rivers <LOC>Rednitz</LOC> and <LOC>Pegnitz</LOC> converge ?
What <LOC>U.S.</LOC> state is <LOC>Dixville Notch</LOC> in ?
Where was the <LOC>Cisalpine Republic</LOC> , 1797-185 , ?
What is the protagonist 's name in <PER>Dostoevski</PER> 's `` The Idiot '' ?
What penalty space lies between <LOC>Baltic Avenue</LOC> and <LOC>Reading Railroad</LOC> on a Monopoly board ?
What presidential press secretary dismissed Watergate as a third-rate burglary attempt ?
What is a meerkat ?
Who was <PER>Jean Nicolet</PER> ?
What kind of animal was <PER>Winnie the Pooh</PER> ?
Which of these are authors ?
What 's the international radio code word for the letter B ?
Who was the original <PER>Humpty Dumpty</PER> ?
What is cache memory ?
Aspartame is also known as what ?
Where is the location of the <LOC>Orange Bowl</LOC> ?
When is President <PER>Nixon</PER> 's birthday ?
What is the origin of the midwest slang , ` you 're darn tootin ' ?
Whose cupboard was bare ?
What are the seven seas ?
What does IBM stand for ?
What is the difference between jazz and blues ?
What is the C programming language ?
What 's the name of <PER>Popeye</PER> 's adopted son ?
Who invented the vacuum cleaner ?
What is a ` borrow pit ' ?
What 2th-century fictional character attends <ORG>Pencey Prep School</ORG> ?
How many people in the <LOC>USA</LOC> say their number one source of information is the newspaper ?
Who does <PER>Shakespeare</PER> 's <PER>Antonio</PER> borrow 3 , 0 ducats from ?
Which country is known as `` <LOC>Big Bear</LOC> '' ?
What `` melts in your mouth , not in your hands '' .
How many times a day should you take a prescription marked `` q.i.d . '' ?
What is the origin of the atom ?
Who is the Voyager project manager ?
Which radio stations air the Jim Bohannon Radio Talk Show ?
What two commanders directed the forces in the Battle of El Alamein ?
Name the creator of `` The Muppets '' .
How do I e-mail someone at aol.com from yahoo.com ?
Who replies `` I know '' to Princess <PER>Leia</PER> 's confession `` I love you '' in The Empire Strikes Back ?
What is the meaning of the name Ella ?
What 's the home of <ORG>the Rockettes</ORG> ?
Where can I find all the information I need to know about the English Civil War , 1642-1649 , ?
What is the name of the firm that makes Spumante ?
What sport is played on the largest field ?
Who won the 1967 Academy Award for Best Actor ?
What is after death ?
Name the first private citizen to fly in space .
What was football star <PER>Elroy Hirsch</PER> 's nickname ?
What singer sings `` Oh Boy '' ?
How much pizza do Americans eat in a day ?
What is the website for the <ORG>USA journal</ORG> ?
What army 's motto is Blood and Fire ?
What kind of patent did <PER>Ermal Fraze</PER> get in 1963 ?
What are you hearing when you put a seashell to your ear ?
Why are haunted houses popular ?
Which gender has bigger thighs ?
What <LOC>U.S.</LOC> state has the second-longest coastline ?
What state 's home to the <LOC>Buffalo Bill Historical Center</LOC> ?
How fast do cheetahs run ?
What is <PER>Ray Bradbury</PER> 's illustrated man illustrated with ?
How fast is a 45Mhz processor ?
What kind of puzzle first appeared in the <LOC>U.S.</LOC> in the <ORG>New York World</ORG> on December 21 , 1913 ?
What count did <PER>Alexandre Dumas</PER> write about ?
What are the odds of giving birth to twins ?
What is the largest natural lake in <LOC>Pennsylvania</LOC> ?
How far is <LOC>London</LOC> <LOC>UK</LOC> from <LOC>California</LOC> ?
Name the two mystical ravens <PER>Odin</PER> has at his command .
What was the species of <PER>Winnie the Pooh</PER> ?
What is the virus HIV ?
How many years old is <PER>Benny Carter</PER> ?
What <PER>Hermann Hesse</PER> book gave its name to a rock group ?
Where does the <LOC>Santa Fe Trail</LOC> begin and end ?
What book is the follow-up to Future Shock ?
What African animals are known as The Big Five ?
What is the alphabet for Latin ?
What is the fear of frogs ?
Which city in <LOC>Canada</LOC> is the least-populated ?
How old is <PER>Stevie Wonder</PER> ?
Who was the first Taiwanese President ?
Who is <PER>Luke Skywalker</PER> 's father ?
What does a dipsomaniac crave ?
What is the definition of the term `` weapons system '' ?
What are <PER>Christopher Marlowe</PER> 's and <PER>Shakespeare</PER> 's literary contributions to English literature ?
What is <PER>Nero Wolfe</PER> 's favorite drink during office hours ?
What is the first personal computer company ?
What is the most efficient way to start a barbeque ?
Who was <PER>Jane Goodall</PER> ?
Why are there Braille things on the ATM machines that people drive through ?
Where is the <LOC>Isle of Man</LOC> ?
What book did <PER>Aaron Hass</PER> write ?
What was the death toll at the eruption of <LOC>Mount Pinatubo</LOC> ?
When will the millennium officially begin ?
Who created the comic strip , `` Garfield '' ?
Which Vietnamese terrorist is now a <ORG>UN</ORG> delegate in <LOC>Doonesbury</LOC> ?
What is real time processing ?
What do we call the imaginary line along the top of the <LOC>Rocky Mountains</LOC> ?
What country 's capital is <LOC>Lagos</LOC> ?
Where does <PER>Ray Bradbury</PER> 's Chronicles take place ?
Who is the current prime minister and president of <LOC>Russia</LOC> ?
Who established a Viking colony in <LOC>Greenland</LOC> about 985 ?
What was the distinguishing mark on the `` Little Rascals '' dog ?
What is the latitude and longitude of <LOC>El Paso</LOC> , <LOC>Texas</LOC> ?
Where can I get information about cystic fibrosis ?
Where did <PER>Honecker</PER> rule ?
What is the theory of equivalence states ?
What does a philatelist collect ?
What is the life span of the average monkey ?
How many member states are in the <ORG>UN</ORG> ?
Who shot and killed himself while painting Wheatfield with Crows ?
What will happen when sodium is put in water ?
What 's the meaning of UOL ?
What future President became <ORG>Senate</ORG> majority whip under <PER>Harry Truman</PER> ?
Who was the architect of <LOC>Central Park</LOC> ?
Which operating system runs on IBM-compatible machines ?
What are the dimensions of an ice hockey goal ?
When was <ORG>CNN</ORG> 's first broadcast ?
What are the signs of a country going into a recession ?
What is the circumorbital hematoma ?
What African country is governed from <LOC>Ouagadougou</LOC> ?
What was the Christian name of the title character in Our Miss Brooks ?
What hard-of hearing artist painted Sunflowers ?
Who were the Yankee 's frequent enemies ?
Who wrote Sons and Lovers ?
What is the English translation for the word `` caliente '' ?
What handicraft requires you to interlace your warp and weft ?
What French seaport claims to be <LOC>The Home of Wines</LOC> ?
How long does it take sunlight to reach <LOC>Earth</LOC> ?
How many milliseconds in a second ?
What Cherokee Indian gave his name to a tree ?
When were camcorders introduced in <LOC>Malaysia</LOC> ?
What is the chance of conceiving quadruplets ?
Who was the star of Leave It to Beaver ?
What countries have the largest armed forces in the world ?
What was <PER>William F. Cody</PER> 's better-known name ?
How do I increase my biceps ' size ?
Who did <PER>Richard Nixon</PER> tender his resignation to ?
Who was <PER>Thucydides</PER> ?
How is the element strontium purified ?
Which of the following rock 'n roll stars has a `` star '' on <LOC>Hollywood Boulevard</LOC> ?
What are tonsils for ?
What molecules include fluorine , sodium and magnesium ?
What was the name of the ball game played by the mayans ?
What was the sequel to The Moon 's Balloon ?
What is the exchange rate for Australian to American money ?
What is the origin of the word ` posh ' ?
How can anyone tell if a female had sexual intercourse ?
How many states did <PER>Richard Nixon</PER> carry in 1972 ?
What basketball maneuver did <PER>Bert Loomis</PER> invent ?
What is a good book to read for people who hate to read ?
How many shillings more than 2 were there in a guinea ?
What does a tarantula eat ?
What are the three secondary colors ?
What does the name `` Sabrina '' mean ?
Who took over as conductor of the <ORG>Boston Pops</ORG> after <PER>Arthur Fiedler</PER> 's long reign ?
What were the trials called which followed World War II ?
What is hebephrenia ?
What Nazi leader killed himself in jail just before he was to be executed as a war criminal ?
What famous events have happened on March 27 ?
Which company claimed to be `` the world 's biggest toy store '' ?
What brand number graces the black label of a bottle of Jack Daniel 's ?
What do I call the sons and daughters of my first cousins ?
What were the causes of the Civil War ?
What are Maid-Rites ?
What city is terrorized by <PER>Dracula</PER> in The Night Stalker ?
How can you prevent it ?
What do the names Andrew and Christina mean ?
What chocolate bar created by <PER>Frank Mars</PER> and his wife is often called a Milky Way with peanuts ?
Who is the fastest guitarist ?
What do camels store in their humps ?
What is the name of the second space shuttle ?
What is the best hospital for orthopedics in the country ?
What are perfect tenses ?
What is commonly considered the fifth sense ?
What was another name for <LOC>East Germany</LOC> ?
What 's the second-biggest-selling magazine in <LOC>America</LOC> ?
Who betrayed <LOC>Norway</LOC> to the <ORG>Nazis</ORG> ?
Who took the toys donated for the <ORG>Doodyville Orphans</ORG> ' Fund and kept them for himself ?
What is a bourdon tube ?
What kind of a sports team is the <ORG>Wisconsin Badgers</ORG> ?
Who were the <ORG>Picts</ORG> ?
What do <PER>Caroll Baker</PER> , <PER>Tammy Grimes</PER> , <PER>Debbie Reynolds</PER> , and <PER>Judy Garland</PER> all have in common ?
What is film noir ?
Who is stationed at <LOC>Camp Swampy</LOC> in the comic strips ?
In what year did <LOC>China</LOC> and the <LOC>Republic of Korea</LOC> establish diplomatic relations ?
What causes tuberculosis ?
How tall is the giraffe ?
What actor dressed up as <PER>Santa Claus</PER> and had a once-a-year affair with actress <PER>Shelley Winters</PER> every Christmas for many years ?
What animal was the heat-seeking missile called the Sidewinder named for ?
How long did it take <PER>Stanley</PER> to find <PER>Livingstone</PER> ?
How much of the nation 's children between the ages of two and eleven watch ` The Simpsons ' ?
What lake is <LOC>Sheboygan</LOC> on ?
What are a baseball team 's firemen ?
What is a fear of color ?
What <LOC>Nantucket</LOC> shipwreck killed more divers exploring it than the 52 people it sank with ?
What are the two largest birds on earth ?
Name the four stories contained in <PER>Edith Wharton</PER> 's `` Old New York . ''
What is the largest lake in <LOC>North America</LOC> ?
How many people died because of a smoking problem in 1997 ?
What is chronic constipation a symptom of ?
Who wrote The Look of Love after viewing <PER>Ursula Andress</PER> ?
What is the name of the American swimmer who won seven gold medals in the 1972 Olympics ?
Who claims to have the greatest show on <LOC>earth</LOC> ?
What is Head Start ?
What Honeymooners actress did <ORG>Television</ORG> magazine name as 1953 's most promising star ?
Why can 't women serve in the Navy on board submarines ?
What did the <LOC>Yalta</LOC> Conference lead to ?
What dog was dubbed <PER>The Mortgage Lifter</PER> ?
What is saltpeter ?
What 's the difference between J.D. and LL.M. ?
What kind of organization is ` <ORG>Last Chance for Animals</ORG> ' ?
What was the role of the Medieval Guild ?
Silly putty was invented by whom ?
What should the oven be set at for baking Peachy Oat Muffins ?
How can someone become a federal agent ?
Who invented the paper clip ?
Whom did <PER>Lauren Bacall</PER> marry after her husband <PER>Humphrey Bogart</PER> died ?
How many times in his 16-year <ORG>National Basketball Association</ORG> career was <PER>John Havlicek</PER> a member of the all-star team ?
What city or state do the most gay men live in ?
<PER>Shea</PER> and <PER>Gould</PER> had an office in <LOC>Los Angeles</LOC> for how long before closing it ?
What word occurs 46 , 227 times in the Bible ?
How can you be happy ?
How would someone go about becoming an organ donor ?
What year did <PER>Degas</PER> create the bronze sculpture , `` Fourth Position Front ? ''
What composer was awarded the Medal of Honor by <PER>Franklin D. Roosevelt</PER> ?
How many URL extensions are there ? and what are they ?
How long after intercourse does it take to find out if you are pregnant ?
What does U.S.S.R. stand for ?
Who created the <ORG>Fantastic Four</ORG> , <PER>Hulk</PER> , and <PER>Thor</PER> ?
What is a fear of gravity ?
Who is the composer of `` Canon in D Major '' ?
What did n't <PER>Rocky Marciano</PER> do in his pro boxing career ?
Where are all European and American eels born ?
Who was the author of the novel `` Far From the Madding Crowd '' ?
What is the definition of ` graphic details ' ?
What was `` America 's recessed-filter cigarette '' ?
What kind of dog is <PER>Scooby Doo</PER> ?
What is the function of the appendix ?
What department store heir is responsible for raising a three-ton safe from the underwater wreckage of the Andrea Doria ?
Which sex is twice as likely to contract leprosy ?
What was the first town to be chartered in <LOC>Vermont</LOC> ?
What state has the longest <LOC>Great Lakes</LOC> shoreline ?
What <LOC>U.S.</LOC> state ends with a G ?
How many varieties of twins are there ?
What is a Cartesian Diver ?
What are the largest libraries in the <LOC>US</LOC> ?
How many people live in the <LOC>Falklands</LOC> ?
Who was <LOC>Camp David</LOC> named for ?
What document did President <PER>Andrew Johnson</PER> want a copy of placed under his head upon his burial ?
Who portrayed `` the man without a face '' in the movie of the same name ?
What happened in <LOC>dogtown</LOC> in 1899 to make that year remembered ?
What wheel did <PER>Blaise Pascal</PER> invent in a search for perpetual motion ?
How much money was the minimum wage in 1991 ?
In what year was the first patent for the pull-tab opener on cans obtained ?
What country boasts the most dams ?
What is the regular price ?
What <LOC>Metropolis</LOC> landmark was first introduced in the Superman cartoons of the 1940 's ?
Where can one find <LOC>Mozambique</LOC> ?
How do you recognize anorexia ?
What Mary Tyler Moore Show regular came into the world as <PER>Tadeus Wladyslaw Konopka</PER> ?
In what city is the <LOC>US</LOC> Declaration of Independence located ?
What is the largest variety of cactus ?
Who won the first World Series ?
What did <PER>Aaron Hass</PER> write ?
Who is <PER>Samuel Pickering</PER> ?
What was the business of the animated Sky Hawks ?
Who was credited with saying : `` I never met a man I did n't like '' ?
What overalls are named for <LOC>Dungri</LOC> , a suburb of <LOC>Bombay</LOC> ?
Why do rooftops give off steam after a big rainstorm ?
What nationality was <PER>Jackson Pollock</PER> ?
How much of the <LOC>earth</LOC> 's surface is permanently frozen ?
What is the connection between <LOC>New Krypton</LOC> and <LOC>Daxam</LOC> ?
When was Queen <PER>Victoria</PER> born ?
How many people were executed for <PER>Abraham Lincoln</PER> 's assassination ?
What must a <LOC>Las Vegas</LOC> blackjack dealer do when he reaches 16 ?
What is worth seeing in <LOC>Reims</LOC> ?
What type of performer is <PER>Ileana Cotrubas</PER> ?
When was <LOC>Yemen</LOC> reunified ?
What line of candy products included Super Skrunch and Peanut Butter Oompas ?
Why did the <ORG>Anglican church</ORG> split from the <ORG>Vatican</ORG> ?
What organization has a Security Council ?
How would I find the price of different organs that have been donated ?
What Mexican leader was shot dead in 1923 ?
What does NECROSIS mean ?
What is magnetar ?
What feud ended with a marriage in <LOC>Kentucky</LOC> on March 21 , 1891 ?
What color is the stripe along each side of a Coho salmon ?
What is the federal minimum wage ?
<LOC>Mississippi</LOC> is nicknamed what ?
What are the unemployment statistics for the years 1965 and 1990 ?
Where is <LOC>Santa Lucia</LOC> ?
What female painter produced primitives of rural <LOC>New England</LOC> life ?
What are names of two old men who appear in the serial tv Muppets Show ?
What war saw battles at <LOC>Parrot 's Beak</LOC> and <LOC>Black Virgin</LOC> ?
What should you yell to hail a taxi in <LOC>Madrid</LOC> ?
What is the horsepower of the shuttle boosters ?
What year did Apartheid start ?
Who created <LOC>Big Ben</LOC> ?
What city is found in the <LOC>city of OZ</LOC> ?
What ever happened to the once popular <ORG>Yale Lock Company</ORG> ?
Name the <ORG>Marvel</ORG> team loosely based on <ORG>DC</ORG> 's <ORG>Justice League of America</ORG> ?
What did a 16th-century Aztec athlete get for putting a rubber ball through a ring ?
What populous state covers 49 , 576 square miles ?
What college football team did <PER>Knute Rockne</PER> build into a power ?
In what state was there an 11 million gallon oil spill ?
When did <PER>Aldous Huxley</PER> write , `` Brave New World '' ?
What country did the ancient Romans refer to as <LOC>Hibernia</LOC> ?
In what high-risk business venture did <PER>Jimmy the Greek</PER> bet and lose ?
What do chefs call The Master Spice ?
What is the abbreviation of <ORG>General Motors</ORG> ?
What is a Devo hat ?
How long was the longest hiccup attack ?
What kind of weapons were used in Medieval warfare ?
How many people live in <LOC>Tokyo</LOC> ?
What fruit-topped actress was known as <PER>The Brazilian Bombshell</PER> ?
What are birds descendents of ?
When the <PER>Tutankhamun</PER> exhibit was on display in the <LOC>U.S.</LOC> , what moving company transported it ?
